> > Brian Holt: 如果我想做动画怎么办 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what happens if
I want to do an animation, right?
如果我想旋转狮子狗怎么办
What happens if I want to spin the poodle?
谁不想把狮子狗转了对吧
Who doesn't want to spin the poodle,
right?
所以我们要做的就是进口
So what we're gonna do here
is we're going to import.
> > Brian Holt: 我们可以摆脱这个点击句柄，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We can get
rid of this onclick handle,
把我逼疯了好吗
it's driving me crazy, okay.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，从情绪/核心开始，我们还将导入关键帧和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So here from emotion/core,
we're also going to import keyframes and
然后我们说 const spin = 关键帧
then we're gonna say,
const spin = keyframes.
我们要做另一个标记的模板文字，像那样的关键帧。
We're gonna do another tagged template
literal, keyframes like that.
> > Brian Holt: 我们在这里做一个非常简单的转型，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're just gonna do
a pretty simple transformation here,
我们要对 { 变换 : 旋转 (360 度) :
which we're gonna say to {
transform: rotate (360 deg):.
因此，这不是动画类。
So again, this is not a animation class.
莎拉教了非常好的动画课程
Sarah teaches really
good animation classes.
>> Brian Holt: 但如果你说，你会省略，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
if you say to and you omit from, and
只是假设你要从目前的状态到 360 度
it just assumes that you're going from
the current state to 360 degrees.
一切都会好的好吧这会是个旋转
Which would be all way around,
right, which is gonna be a spin.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 所以现在我要做的就是去做贵宾狗。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now what I'm gonna
do is I'm gonna go down to the poodle.
> > Brian Holt: 我要说， >> Brian Holt: Animation，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And I'm going to say,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Animation,
我想你应该说的是显示器
I think you're gonna have to say,
display:, rather.
内联 block; >> Brian Holt: 和动画:
Inline-block;
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And animation:
>> Brian Holt: 1s $ 线性无限;
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: 1s $ linear infinite;
>> Brian Holt:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So spin will
实际上包含它为您生成的动画的名称，是吗 ?
actually contain the name of the animation
that it generates for you, right?
现在，我们有一个非常困惑的狮子狗。
And so now,
we have a very confused poodle.
>> Brian Holt: 请进行检查，以便在悬浮时执行。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Check this out,
so you could do on hover.
我们可以把这变成这样，然后说反话。
We can move this into this and
say reverse.
>> Brian Holt: 这很有趣。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's wildly entertaining.
这是很好的品牌工作，把人的眼睛给品牌，对吧 ?
This is good brand work cuz it brings
people's eyes to the brand, right?
应该在市场营销中工作，现在是 Brian Holt 的市场营销主子。
Should work in marketing, this is now
marketing masters with Brian Holt.
[LAUGH] >> 演讲者 2: 有关此提醒的内容
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Something about this reminds
我是安其火的人
me of Angelfire.
>> Brian Holt: [LAUGH] 有关它的所有内容都应该提醒您安其火。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: [LAUGH] Everything about
it should remind you of Angelfire.
颜色调色板，可笑的边界，旋转的狮子狗。
The color palette, the just ridiculous
borders, the spinning poodle.
这是我的地理城市，对吧 ?
This was my Geocities site, right?
>> 扬声器 2: [LAUGH] >> Brian Holt: I
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I
我上次来的时候是这样做的
think the last time I was here,
I made it so
每次你点击狗的时候，它的速度更快，速度更快。
every time you clicked on the poodle,
it spun faster and faster.
直到最终都是模糊的，看起来就像在向后旋转。
Until eventually it was a blur and
it looked like it was spinning backwards.
但是你现在知道怎么做了对吧
[LAUGH] But you know exactly
how to do that now, right?
你要做的就是跟填料做同样的事
All you have to do is the same
thing we do with padding.
你只会把这个 1s 替换为半秒，八分之一，第八秒，对吧 ?
You would just replace this 1s with
half s, quarter s, eighth s, right?
最终你会喜欢的是 0.1 个S，对吧 ?
And eventually you get down to like,
0.1S, right?
>> 演讲者 2: [LAUGH] >> Brian Holt:
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And you end up with
那样的东西对吧
something like that, right?
>> Brian Holt: 所以这就是为什么我对Ev议案感到非常兴奋，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is why I'm
really excited about Emotion, right?
你能做很多很酷的事情
You're able to do a lot of
really cool stuff that was
不可能去做，但是更难。
not impossible to do before,
but much more difficult.
因为你所有的东西都是融合在一起的
Now, because all of your
stuff is melded together,
操纵这类东西真的很容易
it's really easy to manipulate
this kind of stuff.
我是个大粉丝
So, I'm a big fan.
我是一个很大的粉丝他们在推动 CSS 的世界
I'm a big fan in the sense of they're
really pushing the world of CSS
我对此表示高度赞赏。
forward and
I have a great appreciation for that.
所以我们会得到一些叫胡迪尼的东西
So, we're actually gonna get something
called Houdini really quick where you're
实际上可以控制浏览器如何绘制 CSS 属性。
actually gonna be able to control how
the browser paints CSS properties.
现在是他们一直在工作的规范，但是你真的搞砸了
It's a spec that they've been working on
for a while now, but you can actually mess
有一个胡迪尼内置的特殊版本的火狐。
around with a special version of
Firefox that has Houdini built into it.
最终，我认为这将会开始合并更多的
So eventually, I think this is
going to start merging more and
更多地使用浏览器。
more with the browser.
所以我很兴奋。
So I'm pretty excited about it.
所以，如果你想看看这个，就在枝条的枝条上。
So if you want to check this out,
this is in the branch Emotion.
不幸的是，这不是一起旋转的贵宾犬。
Does not come with spinning poodle,
unfortunately.
这不是快速旋转的狮子狗
Well, it doesn't come with
fast spinning poodle.
它是用正常的旋转的狮子狗来的
It comes with normal spinning poodle.